{
    "subject": "Sarah_Mlynowski",
    "predicate": "isCitizenOf",
    "object": "Canada",
    "human_readable": "Sarah Mlynowski is a citizen of Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884472489356995,
            "question": "Is Sarah Mlynowski a Canadian citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9174262285232544,
            "question": "Is Canada the home country of Sarah Mlynowski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9006839394569397,
            "question": "What country is Sarah Mlynowski a citizen of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8438995480537415,
            "question": "What is Sarah Mlynowski's citizenship status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7711760401725769,
            "question": "Where is Sarah Mlynowski from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6758465766906738,
            "question": "Where does Sarah Mlynowski reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6575015783309937,
            "question": "To which country does Sarah Mlynowski belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.597486674785614,
            "question": "What is Sarah Mlynowski's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5920694470405579,
            "question": "In what country was Sarah Mlynowski born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5425581932067871,
            "question": "If Sarah Mlynowski were to travel internationally, would she need a passport?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sarah Mlynowski is a citizen of Canada.",
            "html": "yago_14820_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was Sarah Mlynowski born?",
            "html": "yago_14820_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sarah Mlynowski's nationality?",
            "html": "yago_14820_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Sarah Mlynowski belong?",
            "html": "yago_14820_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14820_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Sarah Mlynowski is a citizen of Canada. This is mentioned in several documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14820/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14820/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt, which both state that she is a \"Canadian writer\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Sarah Mlynowski (born January 4, 1977) is a Canadian writer,\" which supports the statement that Sarah Mlynowski is a citizen of Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}